Jackson College Handbook UP076
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Jackson College Handbook
1911 -- 1970
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Publications
UP076
0.75 Linear Feet
61 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains annual issues of Jackson College Handbook between 1911 and 1970. It is an annual booklet containing rules, regulations, and information for students of Jackson College.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Publications is one of four departments comprising Tufts Office of Communications. This Office is responsible producing magazines, newsletters, and marketing material for Tufts University. Through design and writing the Office of Publication aims to capture and share the visual and intellectual identity of the University. The Office also offers editorial, design, and project management services for Tufts departments, and maintains external contracts with photographers and design firms.
- Jackson College Handbook, 1911 -- 1970; UP076.001; 0.75 Linear Feet; 61 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains annual issues of the Jackson College Handbook between 1911 and 1970.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Jackson College Regulations, 1911 -- 1936; UP076.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1911; UP076.000016; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, 1914; UP076.000017; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, 1914; UP076.000019; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, 1915; UP076.000018; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, 1916; UP076.000022; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, 1917; UP076.000021; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rules and Regulations of the Association for Self-Government of the Students of Jackson College, circa 1918; UP076.000023; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and Regulations of the Student Government Association of Jackson College, 1921; UP076.000059; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - College Regulations, 1921-1922; UP076.000020; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and Regulations of the Student Government Association of Jackson College, 1924; UP076.000058; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1925; UP076.000037; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1926; UP076.000030; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1927; UP076.000031; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1928; UP076.000057; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1929; UP076.000027; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1930; UP076.000038; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1931; UP076.000028; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1933; UP076.000025; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1933; UP076.000036; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1935; UP076.000026; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1935; UP076.000032; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1936; UP076.000029; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1937; UP076.000033; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1939; UP076.000024; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1939; UP076.000034; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jackson College Regulations, 1937 -- 1952; UP076.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1940; UP076.000045; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1941; UP076.000044; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1942; UP076.000056; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1945; UP076.000060; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1946; UP076.000043; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1947; UP076.000042; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1948; UP076.000041; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1949; UP076.000040; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1950; UP076.000039; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1951; UP076.000047; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1952; UP076.000046; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jackson College Regulations, 1952; UP076.000035; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1953 -- 1957; UP076.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1953-1954; UP076.000062; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1954-1955; UP076.000049; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1955-1956; UP076.000050; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1955-1956; UP076.000064; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1957 -- 1960; UP076.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Chironian Honors Top Sophomores, 1957; UP076.000052; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1957-1958; UP076.000055; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - College Honesty, 1958; UP076.000053; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College New Student Welcome Letter, 1959; UP076.000054; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1957-1958; UP076.000065; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1958-1959; UP076.000061; 1 Digital Object(s); 20 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1959-1960; UP076.000063; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Tufts University Student Council, 1960; UP076.000051; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College 50th Anniversary, circa 1960; UP076.000048; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1959 -- 1960; UP076.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1960; UP076.000070; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1960 -- 1963; UP076.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1960-1961; UP076.000066; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1961-1962; UP076.000067; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1962-1963; UP076.000068; 1 Digital Object(s); 25 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1963 -- 1964; UP076.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1963-1964; UP076.000069; 1 Digital Object(s); 24 Megabytes (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1964 -- 1965; UP076.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1964-1965; UP076.000071; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1965 -- 1966; UP076.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1965-1966; UP076.000072; 1 Digital Object(s); 22 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1966 -- 1967; UP076.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1966-1967; UP076.000073; 1 Digital Object(s); 4 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1966-1967; UP076.000074 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1967 -- 1968; UP076.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1967-1968; UP076.000075; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1968 -- 1969; UP076.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1968- 1969; UP076.000076; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jackson College Handbook, 1969 -- 1970; UP076.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - Jackson College Handbook, 1969-1970; UP076.000077; 1 Digital Object(s); 6 Megabytes (Box 2, Folder 7)